Katerine Witkoski

ka.lwitkoski@gmail.com

LinkedIn Github

Site Jundiaí, São Paulo

Summary

I am a third year undergraduate student at Anhembi Morumbi - Paulista pursuing a degree minor in Computer Science and specializing in front end developer. Tech Skills: R (Data analysis), Java, Python, SQL (PostgreSQL, MariaDB, mySQL), JavaScript, CSS, HTML, CI/CD, Fast API, Flask, C, Git

Education

Universidade Anhembi Morumbi, São Paulo, Av. Paulista - Computer Science (2022 - currently)

Adults Star - Curso de Inglês, British and American English School, Jundiaí (2024 - currently)

Universidade São Judas Tadeu, São Paulo - Bachelor in Law (2017 - 2022)

Work Experience

» Ânima HUB (June 2023 – December 2023)

São Paulo — Researcher in the scientific initiation and extension project, Growth Hacker at the BusinessLab laboratory - UAM, supported by the technological research and extension area.

• Development of a scraper in Python and Postgresql to extract data from the Cadastro Nacional da Pessoa Jurídica (CNPJ).

» Freelance Data Analyst (January 2022 - July 2022)

São Paulo

Collected, organized, analyzed and interpreted large volumes of academic research data.

» Associação Brasileira de Jurimetria (Setember 2019 - July 2022)

São Paulo — Full Researcher - Remoto

Mapping strategic and management tasks, including contact with prospective clients. Project monitoring, automation control (GitHub actions), research quality management, organization of tasks and documents, resource mapping, mapping of ABJ's internal processes, compliance with LGPD, analysis and research in the area of Law and development and script maintenance in R.

» Núcleo de Estudos e Pesquisa em Insolvência - NEPI/PUC-SP (January 2021 - December 2021)

São Paulo - Researcher - Remoto

Empirical studies of the processes related to judicial recoveries. Data analysis using R language.

Additional Information

- Core courses: Fast API, HTTP, JavaScript, Python, Dashboards (Shiny), Web scraping Deploy, Data science using R. But my current focus is developing full stack applications using React.js, REST, Python and SQL.
- I am available to work in São Paulo, including remote, in-person, or hybrid arrangements, as well as in nearby regions.